[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 36? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "4069.44",
      "options": [
        "4067.94",
        "4072.44",
        "4070.94",
        "4069.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 29? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2640.74",
      "options": [
        "2642.24",
        "2639.24",
        "2640.74",
        "2643.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 27? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2289.06",
      "options": [
        "2289.06",
        "2287.56",
        "2290.56",
        "2292.06"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 15? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "706.5",
      "options": [
        "705.0",
        "706.5",
        "708.0",
        "709.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 29? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2640.74",
      "options": [
        "2639.24",
        "2640.74",
        "2642.24",
        "2643.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 19? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1133.54",
      "options": [
        "1132.04",
        "1135.04",
        "1133.54",
        "1136.54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 2? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "12.56",
      "options": [
        "12.56",
        "11.06",
        "14.06",
        "15.56"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 16? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "803.84",
      "options": [
        "806.84",
        "802.34",
        "803.84",
        "805.34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 8? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "200.96",
      "options": [
        "203.96",
        "202.46",
        "200.96",
        "199.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 33? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3419.46",
      "options": [
        "3419.46",
        "3422.46",
        "3420.96",
        "3417.96"
      ]
    }
]